I said I'd pay you back.
I'm working to pay you back.
Why are you harassing me like this?
Are you going to tell them that I'm a murderer?
Do you want them to kick me out?
Why are you doing this to me?
Do you think I'm that kind of person?
Right. Whatever.
Anyway, let's go back.
Let me go! Let me go!
Let's go back.
Let me go. What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Yes, I'm crazy.
I'm crazy missing you.
Stay with me.
If you don't stay with me, I'll spread rumors about you.
I'll follow you everywhere you go.
If that can make you stay with me,
I'll do that.
Why?
You said you hate to see me. Why are you doing this?
You were with Ahn Do Hoon on that day.
I'm curious what did you do that day.
Don't try to run away from me.
Is that a good reason?
He has nothing to do with me.
Then, you don't care what I do to Ahn Do Hoon?
It's me.
Fire Ahn Do Hoon right away.
No reason! Do as I say!
- Sir! - Call other firms and tell them not to hire him.
What are you doing?
Why?
What does he mean to you?
Tell me.
Get off.
Is this where you wanted to take me?
Go to work tomorrow.
What?
Go to the western restaurant as usual.
Get off.
We're going to donate the money wecollect from the wedding to the Shina Gallery.
I think the K Corporation should do the same, for the company's reputation.
We pay for the wedding ceremony,
and donate the money to the Shina Gallery?
You chose chinaware from Germany.
How much do you need?
We have about 1,000 guests.
You should choose something like this,
just like we do,
you have a unique taste, don't you?
I don't want to see your friends at the wedding ceremony.
I can't invite my friends to my son's wedding?
If you were Min Hyuk's real mother,
I wouldn't have said that.
That's what you two should decide.
It has nothign to do with me.
If you'll excuse me.
Min Hyuk.
All I have to do is to attend the wedding ceremony, right?
Mother.
What? How can she get back?
The CEO told the manager to hire her back.
That's why he looked a little down.
How does she know the CEO?
Welcome. Thank you for coming.
Hey! Driver! Get in!
I said get in!
Yoo Jung, he's offering us a ride. Don't refuse it.
Let's get in. Let's go. Thanks.
Wow! This car is really nice. Isn't it, Yoo Jung?
You drive so well.
Is there anything you can't do?
By the way, Mr. Jo, how did you meet Yoo Jung?
Hae Ri.
Stop talking please.
By the way, did you thank him?
For what?
He scolded the manager for firing you
and asked him to bring you back.
He said, "How can a manager don't believe his employee?"
He looked so cool.
Have dinner with us.
You drove us here. Have dinner with us.
Hae Ri, they're not eating here.
You can go.
Sir, Yoo Jung is an excellent cook.
You'll regret it if you don't try it.
I'll not have dinner here, I need to talk to you.
Ha.
Hey.
You said you wanted to talk to me.
Don't you want to say something?
I don't know what you want me to say.
But I have nothing to say.
Then don't say anything, I'll find it out.
There's nothing for you to find out.
Okay. Keep saying that.
- Sir! - That bakery. The location isn't great, and the location isn't great,
I can't sell it anyway.
The longer I have it, the more money I lose.
Pay off your debt and take it back.
Kwang Soo.
Yes.
Let's go.
How rude he is to our home
while we are eating.
Min Hyuk!
What are you doing?
Your tuxedo is ready. Try it on.
I told you not to touch that.
When your father threw everything that belonged to your mother away...
I was the one who kept this.
So? Do you want me to thank you?
No. I just wanted to listen to it.
Are you sure he wanted to meet us here?
Yes, his secretary called me to have dinner here.
- He has a secretary! - Okay.
Sit up straight.
Our son works here. Don't be intimidated.
Oh my god! Who is this?
-Hello. - Did Do Hoon invite you as well?
No, it's actually me who invite you two here.
- Se Yeon. - Sorry I didn't tell you in advance.
I really enjoyed the dinner the other night. I want to treat you in return.
You don't have to do this.
I relly enjoyed that. I really want to join you,
but I still have some work to do at the moment.
- Enjoy your meal. - Thank you.
She looks very charming.
What on earth does she do?
She is well educated, and she's polite to us.
The hard drive is damaged, so it'll be hard to check the black box records
I think I know who did it. But I don't have evidence now.
You must be curious what's on there as well.
- Yes. - Then recover it.
Ah! Do Hoon! Did you touch other files in the Security Room?
What do you mean?
I heard that some data was damaged.
Min Hyuk asked the tech team to recover it.
What were you looking for that day?
I don't know what you are talking about.
I only looked at the files related to Pyeongchang Construction.
- Really? - Yes.
- You don't have to come with me. - I'll escort you to the airport.
- No. - Sir.
- Don't worry about me. Take good care of Min Hyuk when I'm not here. - Yes, sir.
And...
About Ahn Do Hoon. Don't overpraise him,
we need to be able to beat him when we need to.
Get ready for that.
Let's go.
What did he say?
He's the head of the K Corporation.
He needs to take care of everything.
- Is everything okay with your tasting event? - Yes.
- Here are the plates. - Can you bring somethign for me?
Okay.
This is today's guest list.
- Did Kang Yoo Jung come to work today? - Yes.
Let's go.
- Here are the new dishes. - Here you are.
- Give that to me. - This one?
- Yoo Jung. - Yes.
Mr. Jo is here to see you.
What does he want?
I'll pay you for the day. Go home!
- Sir! - You don't have to work today. Just go.
People are speaking ill of me
because you brought me here.
Sinc I'm working here,
I don't want anything else happened.
Driver, just listen to me.
I don't work and get paid. Why should I do that?
- The guests have arrived. - I have to work.
Hey! Driver!
Mr. Jo.
- Welcome. - Haven't seen you for a long time.
Okay.
Don't let Kang Yoo Jung serve today.
- Well... - What?
- Think about it. - Okay.
Your ribs are ready.
- Do you work here? - Yes.
I'll cut it for you.
What are the qualifications for working here?
I don't know, sorry.
I guess you don't know what shame is.
Why don't we talk about the food?
This is a tasting event. We're not evaluating our employees.
If you're done here, you can go.
I told you to go.
Yoo Jung, is that Do Hoon?
Oh my god! It drives me crazy.
How is this possible?
Yoo Jung, stay here! I'll go.
Hae Ri, bring me some water.
Okay.
Yoo Jung.
I thought you'd quit.
Something happened.
Besides, it's not easy for me to get a job elsewhere.
So you take the job he offerd no matter how bad he is?
You don't know who Jo Min Hyuk is?
You don't know why he's keeping you around?
Do Hoon.
I do hate him.
I heard about the parole thing.
I know everything.
Can't you think for me?
Don't you know why I'm here even I have known everything?
Parole?
What are you talking about?
Okay.
It's none of your business.
I have to work.
What are you talking about?
Get out of the way.
I won't bother you again.
The fact that you're working here
is making my life very difficult.
Is there a reason why I shouldn't work here?
The fact that he knows about our relationship?
So what?
What about it?
I have nothing to do with you now.
You.
Everytime I see you, I suffered a lot.
Everytime you stand in front of me,
it just makes me sick.
Your facilities are perfect.
The employees are effective.
Stop harrassing Kang Yoo Jung.
You said you have nothing to do with her.
I'm wondering why do you keep Yoo Jung near you.
I told you,
I fall in love with her.
The more I know her, the more I find her interesting.
I'm curious.
You're curious.
Curiosity is always a problem.
I'll take care of my employee.
It's none of your business now.
Have you said enough?
I have something to tell you.
Choose one.
That's the least you can do.
It's our weeding, not mine.
What's your relationship with that woman?
You don't need to know.
This marriage is just a business deal.
Hey! Driver!
You were off work so early, why do you come home so late?
I didn't do it on purpose.
You must think I did it.
I used to do it.
But not this time.
Don't get mad at me.
You should've left when I told you to.
Thank you for your concern
Good night.
Not long after we met,
You dumped me.
It's a lie. It's a lie.
Yoo Jung!
My sweet Yoo Jung!
Have a seat!
I bought a bottel of expensive dry wine from China.
Drink some!
You only brought one bottle.
Drink it! For we failed to sell the bags.
I'm so depressed.
I'm really sad and depressed. How can I make a living?
We can drink wine.
Eat it.
Eat this and drink up.
Men's hearts are easy to change.
They would be cruel when they don't love you.
But it's weird that we women would feel lonely when they are not here.
If they are here I would be happy.
Men are annoying. Right?
Sure.
If I can support myself, I don't need a man.
I don't care whether love changes or not.
Love doesn't change. People change.
So you should find a good person.
Hello.
Yoo Jung.
How are you?
What are you doing here so late?
Is this your shop's recipe?
Right.
This is my father's jacket.
Your father always came here to buy a cream cake.
He lived here his entire life.
Whenever he came, his nurse came with him.
But he came alone that day.
Your father looked better.
He recognized me and looked really good.
Are you sure that was the same day?
I'm not sure.
It was pouring down, and a guy came and picked him up.
I thought it was your fiance.
You are really free, you even have time to read.
Thanks to you.
Don't think that you can
control me using the board members.
I told you that wasn't it.
The board already decided....
I don't care.
I don't care even if they dismiss me unanimously,
it's about you,
at least you should support me.
Min Hyuk!
I warned you,
not to get Do Hoon involved.
We
are not even friendes anymore.
Get out of my room.
Let's go.
What?
Min Hyuk wants you to work at his place today.
I've already called the restaurant.
I can't just miss work.
Tell him that I went to the restaurant.
- She's here. - Okay.
Why did you bring me here?
You're my employee.
- Work here today. - What?
The people who work here went on a vacation,
and this place is a mess.
You need to fill in for them.
Clean that up first.
Who are you? Where is Yeongae?
She's on a vacation.
Vacation?
I want to eat something spicy.
It's delicious.
Why don't you have some? It's really good.
Have a seat.
Have you eaten yet?
Try it.
Eat. Go ahead. Come on.
- Isn't it good? - Yes.
That's it?
You're just like my brother. Boring.
- Kwang Soo, what does Gwang Min like? - Excuse me?
What does Gwang Min like to eat?
Cup noodles. He likes cup noodles.
What?
He really enjoyed them when he was little.
Min Hyuk! Try this.
She's a really good cook.
Bring me some coffee.
Continue to eat.
I had some while cooking.
The coffee's in the kitchen, right?
Where should I put it?
I have finished cleaning, there is nothing I can do.
If there's nothing to do, I'll leave.
There must be something to do. Don't go!
Bring it here.
You have something to do. Read this.
Take it.
I want to know how it ends, but I don't want to read it.
Read it and write me a summary.
Right now.
Don't sit there. Go over there and read quietly.
Wow, you do come here.
Do you want me to come to see you like this?
I can only show you this.
What is upsetting you?
Is this because you saw Min Hyuk today?
I thought your wedding plans were going well.
It looks that way to other people.
I feel like I'm drifting apart from him.
You still want to have him even like this?
I don't want to see you torture yourself
because of Min Hyuk.
Stop drinking.
Why weren't you born in a wealthy family?
As long as we are of equal status,
I would've chosen you over Min Hyuk.
No one can choose their parents.
You can't choose your family members. Except your spouse.
You know what?
You gave up the only choice you had the right to make.
If you want to drink, drink yourself.
Ahn Do Hoon!
Come here!
Have a drink. It's for apologize.
I'll call a designataed driver for you.
Sir! Sir!
- I'm leaving. - Okay.
Come to work here tomorrow.
- Sir. - Right. I'm your boss.
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay
Read it. And find out how revenge, which started because of love, ended.
Though you owe his money he can't do this to you.
I don't think he's doing this because of money.
I don't think he wanted me there to torture me.
Pull yourself together. Don't be fooled by that rich guy.
Don't fall for it.
By the way, when will you finish working there?
The manager was unhappy about the dirty table.
He was wondering if he should hire someone.
I'll tell the boss tomorrow.
This isn't right.
Sir.
Em.
Someone already paid your bill.
What are you doing here?
This...
I'm going to wash this.
Excuse me.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Thank you.
For taking me to the hospital
that day.
You saved my life.
Yes.
You owe me.
Go.
What's this? Doesn't it smell nice?
Coo...
I hope we can see your father next month.
Do you think we can see him?
If there is nothing for me to do,
I'll leave now.
I'll go to the restaurant tomorrow.
My colleagues are suffered because of me,
I feel ashamed of that.
Yoo Jung!
Hey!
How dare you come here?
What?
I want to beat her to death, why are you stopping me?
I thought we were done talking.
Why do you come here?
What? You already talked to her?
And you let her go?
Yoo Jung.
I'm so sorry.
I was so shocked,
and I can't sleep at night. I keep thinking of San.
I'm so sorry.
I would regret it all my life without apologizing for you.
If you knew you were wrong,
How can you treat San like that?
How can you even mention San?
I didn't know this'd happen.
I mean it.
Stop yelling!
San was bruised all over.
How could you do that to him?
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that.
Stop, please.
Not knowing doesn't make it okay.
Yoo Jung.
I'm waiting at the door.
I thought you didn't want to see me again.
What happened?
Jo Min Hyuk is reinvestigating the hit-and-run case.
Is that you?
Do Hoon!
Do you feel wronged?
How to explain that you are with Jo Min Hyuk all the time?
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm not.
You were the driver.
You made the decision.
So,
Are you here to make sure?
I also want to make sure of something.
That store near the railroad.
The owner saw you.
On the day that my father went missing.
She said you took my father away.
Is that true?
No.
She must've been mistaken.
Really?
Yes.
You're lying.
You're no good at lying.
Yoo Jung!
What now?
What does he want this time?
This time?
The guy who prevented you from getting parole.
What are you talking about?
He aksed me to prevent you from getting parole.
Say that again.
Are you sure?
Are you sure that was him?
Yes. He was the volunteer of our jail.
It's a piece of cake.
I can tell them someone scratched my car, and get the surveillance camera footage.
If he told you to trust him, you can't trust him.
Never trust anyone.
You stay here.
1st of last month, right?
She's not here?
She called in sick.
What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
Check it out.
What?
Nothing.
I also want to make sure of something.
That store near the railroad.
The owner saw you.
She said you took my father away on the day that my father went missing.
Is that true?
You're lying.
You're no good at lying.
Dad! Dad!
It's dangerous for him to go out alone.
This has his information on it.
He can't take it off on his own.
I don't know where my house is. Take me to Yoo Jung.
Yes, Yoo Jung's worried about you. Get in the car.
You still remember that?
Of course.
You thought I don't know that
you drove the car and make Yoo Jung your scapegoat?